UNITE Publications 6000 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Publications
1980-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000 PUBS
3.5 cubic feet
3.5 linear ft.
Records.
5748401
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, October 30, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Scope and Contents
Publications in English, Chinese and Spanish.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Textile industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; UNITE HERE (Organization)
5748401
- Box: 1, Folder: 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: UNITE (Union of Needeltrades, Industrial and Textile Employees)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1995:Oct.). Copy 2.
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1995:Dec.)
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1995:Dec.). Copy 2.
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1995:Dec.). Copy 3.
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1995:July) Special Convention Issue
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1995:Sep.)
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1995:Sep.). Copy 2.
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1995:Sep.). Copy 3.
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1995:Oct.)
- Box: 1, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1996:Jan./Feb.)
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1996:Jan./Feb.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1996:Jan./Feb.). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1996:Mar./Apr.)
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1996:Mar./Apr.). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1996:Mar./Apr.). Copy 3.
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1996:May/June)
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1996:May/June). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1996:May/June). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1996:July/Aug.). Copy 3.
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1996:Sep./Oct.)
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1996:Sep./Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1996:Sep./Oct.). Copy 3.
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1996:Oct.). Special October Election Issue.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1996:Oct.). Special October Election Issue. Copy 2.
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1996:Oct.). Special October Election Issue. Copy 3.
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1996:July/Aug.)
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1996:July/Aug.). Copy 2.
  - Item 10: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1996:Nov./Dec.)
  - Item 11: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1996:Nov./Dec.). Copy 2.
  - Item 12: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1996:Nov./Dec.). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1997:Jan./Feb.)
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1997:Jan./Feb.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1997:Jan./Feb.). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1997:Mar./Apr.)
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1997:Mar./Apr.). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1997:Mar./Apr.). Copy 3.
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1997:May/June)
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1997:May/June). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1997:May/June). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1997:July/Aug.)
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1997:July/Aug.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.4 (1997:July/Aug.). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1997:Sep./Oct.)
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1997:Sep./Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1997:Sep./Oct.). Copy 3.
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.6 (1997:Nov./Dec.)
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.6 (1997:Nov./Dec.). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.6 (1997:Nov./Dec.). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1998:Jan./Feb.). Copy 3.
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1998:Mar./Apr.)
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1998:Mar./Apr.). Copy 2.
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1998:Mar./Apr.). Copy 3.
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1998:May/June)
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1998:May/June). Copy 2.
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.3 (1998:May/June). Copy 3.
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1998:Jan./Feb.)
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1998:Jan./Feb.). Copy 2.
- Box: 1, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1998:Nov./Dec.). Copy 2.
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1998:Nov./Dec.). Copy 3.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1998:July/Aug.)
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1998:July/Aug.). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1998:July/Aug.). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1998:Sep./Oct.)
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1998:Sep./Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.5 (1998:Sep./Oct.). Copy 3.
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.6 (1998:Nov./Dec.)
- Box: 1, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1999:Winter)
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1999:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1999:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1999:Spring)
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1999:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1999:Spring). Copy 3.
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1999:Summer)
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1999:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1999:Fall/Winter)
  - Item 10: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1999:Fall/Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 11: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1999:Fall/Winter). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (2000:Spring)
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (2000:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (2000:Summer)
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (2000:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (2000:Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (2000:Fall)
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (2000:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (2000). Election Special
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (2000). Election Special. Copy 2.
  - Item 10: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (2000). Election Special. Copy 3.
  - Item 11: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (2000:Winter)
  - Item 12: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (2000:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 13: UNITE!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (2000:Winter). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (2001:Spring)
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (2001:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (2001:Summer)
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (2001:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (2001:Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (2001:Fall)
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (2001:Winter)
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (2001:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (2001:Winter). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (2002:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (2002:Winter). Copy 3.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (2002:Spring)
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (2002:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (2002:Spring). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (2002:Summer)
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (2002:Fall)
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (2002:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (2002:Winter)
- Box: 1, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (2003:Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (2003:Fall)
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (2003:Spring)
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (2003:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (2003:Spring). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (2003:Summer)
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (2003:Summer). Copy 2.
- Box: 1, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (2004:Spring)
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (2004:Spring). Copy 2.
- Box: 1, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Language: English; French; Chinese.
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: UNITE!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: UNITE!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: UNITE!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1995:Oct.). Copy 3.
  - Item 12: UNITE!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (2003:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 15: UNITE!, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (2003:Fall). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Box: 1, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Box: 1, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: UNIDAD!, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Box: 1, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Box: 1, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: UNIDAD!, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Box: 1, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Box: 1, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: UNIDAD!, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Box: 1, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1999:Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 9: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1999:Fall)
  - Item 10: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1999:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 11: UNIDAD!, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1999:Fall). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (2000:Fall). Copy 3.
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: UNIDAD!, 2000; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Box: 1, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (2001:Spring). Copy 3.
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (2001:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 9: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: UNIDAD!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Box: 1, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: UNIDAD!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: UNIDAD!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: UNIDAD!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: UNIDAD!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (2002:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 5: UNIDAD!, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (2002:Summer). Copy 3.
  - Item 6: UNITE! En Espanol, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: UNITE! En Espanol, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: UNITE! En Espanol, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (2002:Fall). Copy 3.
  - Item 9: UNITE! En Espanol, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: UNITE! En Espanol, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: UNITE! En Espanol, 2002; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Box: 1, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: UNITE! En Espanol, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: UNITE! En Espanol, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: UNITE! En Espanol, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: UNITE! En Espanol, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: UNITE! En Espanol, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: UNITE! En Espanol, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: UNITE! En Espanol, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: UNITE! En Espanol, 2003; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Box: 1, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: UNITE! En Espanol, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: UNITE! En Espanol, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: UNITE! En Espanol, 2004; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (2004:Spring). Copy 3.
- Box: 1, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: UNITE! En Espanol, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Author: Knitgoods Workers' Union Local 155
    Notes: v.56:no.2 (1995:Summer)
    Language: English; Spanish.
  - Item 2: Voice, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.56:no.3 (1995:Fall)
  - Item 3: Voice, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.56:no.3 (1995:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 4: Voice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.57:no.1 (1996:Winter)
  - Item 5: Voice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.57:no.1 (1996:Winter). Copy 2.
  - Item 6: Voice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.57:no.2 (1996:Spring)
  - Item 7: Voice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.57:no.2 (1996:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 8: Voice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.57:no.3 (1996:Summer)
  - Item 9: Voice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.57:no.3 (1996:Summer). Copy 2.
  - Item 10: Voice, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Notes: v.57:no.4 (1995:Holiday)